sorry.
すみません
What are you doing?
何してるんですか?
Oh, now?
あ、 今ですか?
I was just taking a video while walking in the park.
今ちょっとこう、公園の中歩きながら動画撮ってたんですけど、
Um, I was just here on a business trip.
あの ー、あれはちょっと、この辺に出張で来てて、
Um, I haven't decided on a hotel yet.
あのー、ホテルとかまだ決まってないんですけど、
I thought I'd take some pictures of the scenery before that.
ちょっとその前に景色撮ろうかなと思ってて
There is a hotel nearby, but I haven't been there yet.
近くにホテルありますけど、 行ってません
Wait, your sister works there or something like that?
え、お姉さんがそこで働いてるとかそういうこと?
No, go.
いや、行ってて
What is it?
なんですか?
No, I say I'm not going, but I'm going to my sister's room.
いやでも、行きませんっておうがお姉さんの部屋に行っているって
thing?
こと?
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうです
No, that's no good.
いや、それはダメでしょ
Um, isn't this the first time we've met?
あのー、初対面じゃないですか?
do not have.
ない
Well, I don't really know what to do when a man and woman meet for the first time.
なんか、やっぱ男女で初対面ってあんま何するか分かんないし
Ah, okay.
あ、いいですよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
What's good?
何が、いいんですか?
Yes, yes.
うん、はい
What, do you mean it's okay if I go with you and something happens?
え、一緒に行って何かあってもいいってこと?
Ah, it's okay.
あ、大丈夫です
Are you serious?
マジですか?
Well then, let's go.
じゃあ、じゃあ行きます
Well, let's go.
じゃあ行きます
Eh, this way?
え、こっち?
yes.
はい
Eh, what was your sister doing?
え、お姉さんこそ何してたんですか?
No, I feel bad because I don't have anything to do.
いや、なんかやることなくて気持ち悪い
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
Were you taking a walk?
散歩してた?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうです
So, do you feel like you called out to them in an appropriate way?
で、適当に声かけたみたいな感じですか?
Isn't that a really bad way to kill time?
あんま良くない暇の潰し方じゃないですかね
Hey, did you talk to some people?
え、何人か声かけました?
First shot?
一発目?
Are you serious?
マジですか?
You're both lucky.
ラッキーですね、お互い
She's so petite at first...huh?
なんかすごい小柄で最初...え、
You're an adult, right?
大人ですよね
I'm an adult.
大人です
Sorry, that's a rude thing to say.
すいません、失礼な言い方です
I was a bit wary, though.
なんかだいぶ、だいぶ警戒してましたけど、
I really feel like I'm alone.
なんか本当に普通に一人でって感じなんですね
yes.
はい
Aren't you in danger?
危ない目に合わないですか?
Isn't it so small and cute?
なんかこんだけ小さくて可愛いじゃないですか?
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay now?
今んとこ大丈夫?
Is it okay if something happens at the hotel while we are meeting for the first time?
初対面で行きながらホテルで、何かあっていいんですか?
If you say so, I don't really care.
って言ったら、別にみたいな
Didn't I tell you?
言ったじゃないですか?
Is it okay?
別にいいんですか?
But again.
改めてですけど
Together with you.
あんま一緒に
Are you serious?
マジですか?
Do you feel like you have bare legs?
もう生足って感じ?
It's quite thin.
だいぶ細いんですね
Yeah.
うん
Is it okay?
別にいいんですか?
Aren't you a minor?
未成年じゃないですか?
Yes, I'm 19 years old.
はい、19歳です
Well then, is it just?
じゃあ、ギリか
Giri.
ギリ
Can I have you stand one more time?
ちょっともう一回立ってもらっていいですか?
Considering the overall size, I feel like it's a bit big.
この全体のサイズ感からするとなんか大きい気がするんですけど
Can you see it?
見えてる?
this.
これ
The shape is beautiful too.
形も綺麗ですね
Your breasts are beautiful.
おっぱい綺麗ですね
The color of the chikubi.
チクビの色さ
This isn't a skirt, is it?
これスカートじゃないよね、これね
Why is it so completely visible?
なんでこんな丸見えなの?
this.
これ
Are you going to drop it?
落とすの?
Is this just my imagination?
これ気のせい?
this.
これ
Is it okay for me to dress like this since I just met you?
さっき会ったばっかりこんな格好していいんですか?
Can I ask you to shift this yourself?
自分でこれずらしてもらっていいですか?
At the hotel.
ホテルに
This is how it happened.
こうなったんですけど
Hyul-san, do you know something?
ヒョルさん、何か分かる?
girl.
女の子
Do you have one of your own?
自分のやつ持ってたりしますか?
Have you ever used it?
使ったことある?
surely.
確かに
Something like this.
なんか、これ、こういうの
Was it ticklish?
きすぐったかった?
Yeah.
うん
I guess being ticklish is a different matter.
きすぐったいことはまた別かなって言うんだけど
Isn't this place ticklish?
この辺はきすぐったいないの?
Yeah.
うん
It's a waste of tickle.
きすぐったいないんだ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
My body was tingling, but is it okay?
体、ウネウネしたけど、大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I feel kind of exhausted, are you okay?
なんかぐったりしてるけど、大丈夫?
It's pink.
ピンクになってる
You're bleeding, are you okay?
銃血してきてるけど、大丈夫?
I want you to lick me properly.
しっかり舐めてもらいたいんだけど
After all, it's seriously beautiful.
やっぱりマジで綺麗ですね
The shape is so beautiful.
形がすごい綺麗
The bottom is too small, so it's fine.
下もちっちゃいから、もう
The way you lick it.
舐め方が
Oh, this one is tiny.
あ、こっちちっちゃいね
My mind and body are full.
心身がぶちぶち持ってる
The bottom is a little scary.
下はちょっとやばい
This feels good too though.
こっちも気持ちいいんだけどさ
Like this one.
こっちとかさ
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Can you do well?
よくやれる?
He's a very pleasant child.
めっちゃ気持ちいい子だ
ah.
あー
It doesn't stick to your body or blood.
体、血についないです
It's a little tight, though.
ちょっと、なんか締まりがやばいんだけど
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
Hikari-san, I don't have a rubber band, so I have no choice but to cum inside.
ひかりさん、これゴムないから中出すしかないけど、
good?
いい?
Please let me out.
出してくれよ
good?
いい?
Are you raising your upper body?
上半身を起こしてますか?
Can't you see it yourself?
自分からやつ見えないか